<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>News on The Etherington Group</title><link>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in News on The Etherington Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Website</title><link>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/posts/new-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/posts/new-website/</guid><description>Welcome to the new website of the Etherington Group. Please feel free to explore and have a look around!</description></item><item><title>Group</title><link>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/group/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/group/</guid><description>This page will be populated soon. Check out the publications page as that is going to be populated first.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/publications/</guid><description>2022 Extended Conjugation Attenuates the Quenching of Aggregation-Induced Emitters by Photocyclization Pathways Extended Conjugation Attenuates the Quenching of Aggregation-Induced Emitters by Photocyclization Pathways
Andrew T. Turley, Promeet K. Saha, Andrew Danos, Aisha N. Bismillah, Andrew P. Monkman, Dmitry S. Yufit, Basile F. E. Curchod, Marc K. Etherington &amp;amp; Paul R. McGonigal*
Angewandte Chemie, 134, 24, 2022 From phosphorescence to delayed fluorescence in one step: tuning photophysical properties by quaternisation of an sp 2-hybridised nitrogen atom From phosphorescence to delayed fluorescence in one step: tuning photophysical properties by quaternisation of an sp 2-hybridised nitrogen atom</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/research/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/research/</guid><description>This page will be populated soon. Check out the publications page as that is going to be populated first.</description></item><item><title>Seminars</title><link>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/seminars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/seminars/</guid><description> Key Invited Talk Contributed Talk 2022 From phosphorescence to delayed fluorescence in one step - 13th International Conference of Electroluminescence and Optoelectronic Devices, Chelsea Football Club (UK) Intermolecular interactions in thermally activated delayed fluorescence emitters - SPIE, San Diego Convention Center (USA) Modulation of charge transfer by N-alkylation to control photoluminescence energy and quantum yield - International Conference on the Science and Technology of Synthetic Metals, University of Glasgow (UK) 2021 Thermally activated delayed fluorescnece: Beyond the single molecule - 6th International TADF Workshop, Kyushu University (Japan) - WEBINAR Thermally activated delayed fluorescnece: Beyond the single molecule - NECEM Photophysics for Energy Materials Conference, Newcastle University (UK) - WEBINAR 2020 Capturing tonic water&amp;rsquo;s blue glow for photonic applications - Natural Sciences Hour, University of York (UK) - WEBINAR Capturing tonic water&amp;rsquo;s blue glow for photonic applications - North East Centre for Energy Materials (NECEM), Newcastle University (UK) - WEBINAR Modulation of charge transfer by N-alkylation to control photoluminescence energy and quantum yield - Durham Energy Institute, Durham University (UK) - WEBINAR Controlling charge transfer in tonic water and looking at thermally activated delayed fluorescence beyond the single molecule - Department of Physics, University of Sheffield (UK) - WEBINAR 2019 Persistent dimer emission in thermally activated delayed fluorescence materials - Optical Probes, Vilnius (Lithuania) Persistent dimer emission in thermally activated delayed fluorescence materials - Department of Chemistry, University of Edinburgh (UK) 2018 Excited-state aromatic interactions in the aggregation-induced emission of molecular rotors - WOREN, Wisla (Poland) 2017 Photoinduced absorption meets thermally activated delayed fluorescence: When slow and (quasi-)steady wins the race - Optical Probes, Quebec City (Canada) 2016 Spin-orbit charge transfer mechanism in a thermally activated delayed fluorescence molecule - MQD Workshop, University of York (UK) 2015 Hetero triplet fusion in acene-based organic light-emitting diodes - Optical Probes, Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (China) 2014 Magnetic field effects on the photocurrent of polymer:fullerene solar cells - SpinOS, Himeji (Japan) Recombination pathways in organic photovoltaics observed through spin polarization measurements - Fall MRS, Boston (USA)</description></item><item><title>Teaching</title><link>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/teaching/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://marc-k-etherington.github.io/teaching/</guid><description>This page will be populated soon. Check out the publications page as that is going to be populated first.</description></item></channel></rss>